 {

      "category":
            "Music",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "Aaron",
               "question": "What is Elvis Presley s middle name?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Adam Duritz",
               "question": "Who is the singer of The Counting Crows?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Aretha Franklin",
               "question": "Who was the Queen of Soul?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Bass voice",
               "question": "What is the lowest male voice?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The Beatles",
               "question": "Which famous group was once known as The Quarrymen?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Bon Scott",
               "question": "What was the name of AC / DC s lead singer who died in 1980?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The group XTC",
               "question": "Which group performed the song Dear God?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Madonna Louise Ciccone",
               "question": "What is Madonna s full name"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Johnny Logan",
               "question": "What is the name of the Irish singer who won the Eurovision Song Contest twice?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Jukebox",
               "question": "What is the noisy invention of Louis Glass in 1890 called?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Keith Flint",
               "question": "Who is the frontman of The Prodigy?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Lars Ulrich",
               "question": "Who is the drummer of Metallica?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Los Del Rio",
               "question": "Which group did have a hit with the Macarena?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Michael Jackson",
               "question": "Who did win the most Grammy Awards in the 80?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Eight strings",
               "question": "How many strings has a mandolin got?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "White Christmas",
               "question": "What is the biggest hit of Bing Crosby?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Fenty",
               "question": "What is the surname of the singer Rihanna?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Roxy Music",
               "question": "Which British pop group had a hit called Angel Eyes in the seventies?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Five lines",
               "question": "How many lines has a music staff (or music stave) got?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Johnny Logan",
               "question": "Which singer was nicknamed the Voice of Europe after having wun the Eurovision Song Contest three times?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Ennio Morricone",
               "question": "Who composed the music for the Spaghetti Western The Good, The Bad and The Ugly with Clint Eastwood ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Michael Jackson",
               "question": "Which pop singer married Debbie Rowe?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Amy Winehouse",
               "question": "Which British singer had a hit in 2006 with Rehab ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Austrian",
               "question": "What was Mozart s nationality?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Four strings",
               "question": "How many strings does a violin have?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Holiday",
               "question": "What was Madonna s first top 10 single?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Aqua",
               "question": "Which band had a number 1 hit with \"Barbie Girl\"?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "New York",
               "question": "In which city was John Lennon killed?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Europe",
               "question": "Which rock group had a hit with The Final Countdown?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Canada",
               "question": "Which country does Celine Dion come from?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Kolonel Parker",
               "question": "Who was Elvis Presley s manager?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Quando rondo",
               "question": "Who is the artist of the song imperfect flower"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Youngboy never broke again",
               "question": "Whats does nba youngboy stand for"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Megan Thee Stallion",
               "question": "Who is Tina Snow?"
             }
          ]
    }